자막제작 - 네이트 드라마 24
(http://club.nate.com/24)
'24' Season 2
Epi 6. 01:00 P.M.-02:00 P.M.
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON FOX: 2002/12/03
'24' 지난 줄거리
로저, 만나서 반갑네
Roger, it's good to see you.
I'd like to talk to you about this meeting.
I don't trust the ambassador.
이 회의에 관해 말씀 드릴 게 있습니다
대사를 못 믿겠습니다
그 나라가 제2의 물결을
지원할 가능성이 있습니다
It's possible that his country's
supporting Second Wave.
We want to prevent this incident.
우리는 이 재난을 막고 싶습니다
미국 파일에 접근 권한이 필요합니다
We need access to your files.
I want you to monitor
how they use our intel.
우리 정보가 어떻게 쓰여지는지 감시하도록
대사가 탄 헬기입니다
It's the ambassador's chopper.
It crashed just after takeoff.
이륙 직후 추락했습니다
- 누가 찾아왔어
- 누구요?
- There's a man who needs to talk to you.
- Who is he?
정부요원이야, CTU?
He's from the Counter Terrorism Agency?
난 사이에드 알리라는 사람 몰라요
I told you, I do not know a Syed Ali.
그럼, 왜 그 사람 이름이
당신 컴퓨터에 있죠?
Then how do you explain that his name
is in your personal computer files?
There's a nuclear bomb in Los Angeles.
Do what I tell you. Go now.
LA에 핵폭탄이 있어
지금 당장 가!
Miguel, get over here.
미겔, 빨리 와
LA에 핵폭탄이 있다고 하셨어
There's a nuclear bomb in the city.
- 그럼 빨리 가자
- 안 돼, 메건도 데려가야해
- Let's get outta here.
- Not without Megan.
월드를 만났고
누가 CTU 폭파를 지시했는지 알아냈어
George, I got to Wald. I found out
who commissioned him to take out CTU.
누가 시켰어?
- Who was it?
- It was Nina Myers.
니나 마이어스
니나?
Nina?
니나는 네 아내를 살해했어
근처에 얼씬도 하지마
Nina killed your wife.
I don't want you near her.
내가 그녀에게 보호 허가를 내줘야 하네
(Palmer) I have to grant her
a shadow asylum.
사면을 말씀하시는 겁니까?
That sounds like a pardon, sir.
She has information
that could help us find this bomb.
폭탄을 찾을 수 있는 정보를 가지고 있어
- 뭐예요?
- 그녀를 풀어준대
- What is it?
- They're gonna let her go.
I know you were exposed to high levels
of radioactive materials this morning.
조지, 오늘 아침 다량의
방사능 물질에 노출된 거 알아
니나는 어떻게 할 거야?
I wanna know what your plans are for Nina.
I want the case. I know how she thinks.
나한테 맡겨
난 니나의 사고방식을 알아
If you don't do this, I'll tell District
about your condition. They'll replace you.
날 안 끼워주면 본부에 알려서
자네도 이 일을 못하게 만들 거야
이 이야기는 오후 1시부터 2시 사이에
일어난 일입니다
Palmerjust signed the pardon. So, as soon
as it gets here, we'll start the interrogation.
각하께서 방금 사면서에 서명하셨다니까
문서가 도착하면 심문 시작해
니나에 관한 자료들이에요
- Nina's file.
- I don't need it.
필요 없어
The president's here.
대통령께서 오셨습니다
Mr President...
각하! 각하!
Mr President, can you give us any
details about the helicopter crash?
헬기 추락에 대해서
말씀해 주실 수 있습니까?
- Who was on the aircraft? Any survivors?
- Is it related to the bombing in LA?
탑승자는 누구였습니까?
생존자는 없습니까?
희생자 유가족들에게 알리기 전에
어떤 정보도 드릴 수 없습니다
We can't disclose information
about the crash
until the families of the victims
have been notified.
한가지 말씀드릴 수 있는 것은
But I promise you, there will be
a careful and thorough investigation.
정확하고 세밀한 조사를 할 것이라는 점입니다
- Mr President...
- Let's go.
가지
여러분
We will be putting out a formal statement
as soon as we get those issues resolved,
조사가 끝나는 대로
공식 성명을 발표하겠습니다
그 때까지는 추측보도를
삼가 주시기 바랍니다
and I ask everyone to refrain
from speculation until that time.
No one besides Jenny releases
a statement on the crash.
제니 외에는 이 사건에 대해
언급하지 않도록 하게
No names, no speculation.
And keep the lid on tight.
이름도 안 되고, 추측도 안 되네
철저히 단속하게
물론입니다
Absolutely, sir.
잘 있었어요? 데이빗
Hello, David.
내 허락 없이 어떻게 여기 들어왔지?
How did you get in here
without my authorisation?
당신은 아닐지 몰라도, 사람들은
우리가 부부였다는 사실을 존중해요
We were married for many years. Many
people respect that, even if you don't.
I need to talk to you.
할 얘기가 있어요
We have nothing more to talk about.
You're not my wife any more.
우린 할 얘기 없어
- 당신은 더 이상 내 아내가 아니야
- 우리 얘기가 아니에요
- It's not about us.
- Then what?
그럼, 뭐?
여기서 말고..
Not here. I need to be alone with you.
단 둘이서 할 이야기예요
내가 만약에...
You know what?
당신 얘기에 관심이 있더라도
Even if I were interested in what
you had to say, today is impossible.
오늘은 안 돼
You shouldn't have come here.
여기 오지 말아야 했어
- 정부 운영에 대한 얘기예요
- 그게 어때서?
- It's about your administration.
- What about it?
- 5분이면 되요
- 지금은 시간 없어
- Just give me five minutes.
- I don't have time now.
Did you order an evacuation of
military personnel out of Los Angeles?
군사 요원을 LA 밖으로
대피하라고 명령했어요?
Who told you that?
누구한테서 들었어?
5분만요, 데이빗
Five minutes, David.
Wait here.
여기서 기다려
내가 연락하지
I'll call you.
Do we know about the military
moving personnel out of LA?
군사 요원을 LA 밖으로 대피시켰나?
아니요, 각하께서 대피 명령은
안 된다고 지시하셨지 않습니까?
No. Sir, you specifically requested
there be no evacuation.
- 확인해 봐
- 네, 그러죠
- Check into it.
- I certainly will.
You're doing business
with a known terrorist,
테러범과 사업하고 있으면서
그렇게 굳은 얼굴로
아무것도 모른다고 하실 겁니까?
and you sit there with a straight face
and tell me you don't know what's going on?
전 런던에서 자랐어요
I grew up in London. I'm marrying
an American girl, a Protestant.
미국여자와 결혼할 거고요
물론 기독교인이죠
So, if you're going to racially profile me,
인종 프로파일링을 하려면
똑바로 해요
you should at least get it right.
Our main targets are European Muslims
우리의 주 타깃은 유럽인 이슬람교도로
with western educations, passports,
서양 교육에 서양 여권을 소지했으며
and the potential
to blend into western society.
서구 사회에 자리잡고 있는 사람들이요
어디 말해 보시죠
So tell me, Reza,
how's my racial profiling going now?
내 인종 프로파일링이 어떤지?
변호사 부르겠어요
I want a lawyer.
안 돼요
No.
블랙박스를 아직 못 찾았나?
- Did they find the black box yet?
- Not yet, Mr President.
아직입니다, 각하
젠장! 로저, 어떻게
이런 일이 일어날 수 있지?
How could something like this happen?
모르겠습니다, 각하
우선 합동 조사에 착수했습니다
I don't know. I've opened a multi-agency
investigation. NTSB is on the way.
린, 가능한 빨리 수상과
전화 통화 부탁하네
Lynne, schedule a call
with the prime minister.
네, 각하
- Yes, sir.
- I wanna talk to him before rumours start.
소문이 퍼지기 전에 연락하고 싶네
But I'm afraid they may not be far from
the truth. This was not an accident.
소문이 맞을 지도 모른다는 게 유감이지만
이건 사고가 아니었어
저와 같은 생각이시군요
I'm thinking along
the same lines, Mr President.
The prime minister may not have been happy
about the ambassador's cooperation with us.
대사가 우리와 협력하는 걸
그들 수상이 반대했을 수도 있습니다
다른 가능성도 있네
There's another possibility, Roger.
무슨 말씀이신지
I'm not following you, sir.
- 저희 쪽에서 했다는 거죠
- 맞아
- That we did it.
- Correct.
That hardly seems likely.
그건 불가능한 것 같습니다만
The ambassador took classified
information back to his government.
대사는 기밀 정보를 가져가고 있었어
자네들도 의심하지 않았나?
- You both thought it was questionable.
- And if we were talking about it here,
여기, 오리건에서도 그런 생각이 든다면
워싱턴에선 더 심할 겁니다
you can bet there are others back
in DC who feel even more strongly.
독자적인 조사에 착수해서
Set up an independent investigator.
Let's find out exactly who was in the loop.
- 누가 개입되었는지 알아내게
- 네, 각하
Yes, sir.
OK, this is it. Here we go.
자, 준비됐네
시작하자고
I'll show her this, I'll let her start talking.
서류를 보여주면 입을 열 거야
Then I'll get you the stuff
she doesn't want us to know.
어떻게든 자네가 원하는 정보를 얻어내지
The last time I let you interrogate
somebody, you shot him through the heart.
지난번에 심문을 맡겼을 땐
심장에 총알을 박았었지?
I'm letting you do this,
but I hope I'm not making a mistake.
자네에게 맡기는 게
실수가 아니길 바라네
No mistake, George.
실수 아니야, 조지
알았어, 행운을 비네
All right. Good luck.
Let's keep this simple.
간단히 말하죠
If you wanna stop the bomb,
I need to be on a plane to Visalia now.
폭탄을 제거하고 싶으면
날 지금 바셀리아로 데려가요
바셀레아로 가려는 이유가 있어?
Did you pick Visalia for a reason, or would
anywhere outside the blast zone work?
아니면 폭파 반경 밖을 원하는 거야?
- My contact is in Visalia.
- Who is it?
내 접선자가 바셀리아에 있어요
누군데?
The only person who can
tell us where the bomb is.
폭탄이 어디 있는지
말해줄 수 있는 사람
거기 도착하기 전까진
누군지 말하지 않을 거예요
I'm not gonna tell you who it is
till we get there.
좋아
Fine. Then you can sit here
and wait for the blast to hit.
폭탄이 터질 때까지 거기 죽치고 있어
Stop wasting time.
I have the president's signature.
시간 낭비 말아요
대통령 사면장도 있으니까
난 여기 있지만, 대통령은 여기 없어
I'm here. He's not.
네 말에 믿음이 가지 않는 한
아무것도 하지 않을 거야
And I'm not gonna make a move
until I believe you're credible.
폭탄을 멈춰야 사면될 텐데
왜 내가 최선을 다하지 않겠어요?
I'll only get the pardon if I stop the bomb.
Why wouldn't I do everything I can?
넌 배신자보다 더 나쁘니까
Because you're worse than a traitor, Nina.
넌 이유도 없고, 신념도 없잖아
You don't have a cause.
You don't believe in anything.
But you would sell anyone out
to the highest bidder.
넌 돈만 되면 무엇이든 팔아먹으니까
시간 낭비 마!
So stop wasting my time! Gimme a name!
이름을 대!
Don't even bother, Jack.
이러지 마요
If you lay a hand on me,
you'll be taken off the case.
나한테 손 하나 까딱했다간
이 사건에서 손 떼야 할 테니까
당신은 내가 하자는 대로 해야 할 걸요
You're just gonna have to follow my lead.
Tell me everything I wanna know,
- 내가 원하는 걸 전부 말해
- 문 열어!
or I swear to God, I will hurt you
before I kill you and no one will stop me.
널 죽이고 말 거야
- 아무도 날 멈추지 못 해, 알겠어?
- 풀어줘, 당장
- Do you understand?
- (Mason) Jack, let her go! Now!
(gasps)
자넨 끝이야, 나가
- All right, you're done. Get outta here.
- Why?
왜?
Why? Because you've lost it! That's why.
이성을 잃었기 때문이야, 됐어?
조지, 지금 니나는
로또라도 당첨된 줄 알고 있어
Right now she thinks she's
won the lottery. She's in control.
진실을 캐내려면 그 생각을 없애야 해
You want her to tell the truth, take that away.
By killing her? That'll work.
죽이기라도 해서?
잘도 되겠네
아니, 그녀가 무서워하는
사람을 데려다 놓으면 돼
By giving her someone to answer to,
someone to be afraid of.
내가 복수 때문에 이 일을
하는 것처럼 믿게 해야 돼
She has to believe I'd be willing to put
my revenge over finding this bomb.
- 복수할 생각은 없단 말인가?
- 그렇게 보이려고 했을 뿐이야
- And you're telling me you're not.
- George, it had to look like that.
날 봐
Look at me. There's no emotion here.
아무런 감정이 없어
Now look at her.
그녈 봐
그건 그렇다 치고 이젠 어떻게 할 거지?
- What would your next move be?
- You need to let me go back in there,
다시 들어가게 해줘
내가 자기한테 무슨 짓이든
할 수 있다는 걸 보여줘야 해
show her that I have the power
to do anything I want to her.
- 다시 들여보내 주면...
- 조지, 5분이면 돼
- If I let you go back in there, you've got...
- All I need is five minutes.
Just don't let anyone in that room
and raise the thermostat ten degrees.
아무도 들어오지 못하게 하고
실내온도를 10도만 올려줘
Are you gonna let me have five minutes?
5분 줄 거야?
그래
Yeah.
고마워
Thank you.
In the latest update,
we have Mr President requesting...
얘기 좀 하자
We need to talk.
가라고 했잖아
I told you to leave.
그래?
Well...
I'm not leaving.
난 안가
난 네 언니야
I'm your sister,
and you can stay angry with me,
계속 화내는 건 좋지만
어떻게 할 건지 정해야 해
but we need to figure out
what we're going to do.
뭘 어떻게 해?
Do about what?
The wedding.
결혼식
취소해야 할 지도 몰라
We may have to cancel.
그러면 좋겠다, 그치?
That would make you happy, wouldn't it?
Isn't that what you wanted all along?
처음부터 그걸 원했던 거 아냐?
No. Not the marriage, Marie.
아니야
결혼이 아니라 결혼식만이야
Just the wedding.
오늘은 할 수 없어
We can't do it today.
Let me help you take care of it.
내가 도와줄게
You are always pretending
you wanna help me.
언니는 항상 날 도와주는 시늉을 해
Pretending?
시늉이라고?
엄마가 돌아가셨을 때
난 학교도 그만두고 널 돌봤어
I dropped out of school when Mom died to
take care of you, to keep this family together.
우리 가족을 위해서
그래, 그런 핑계로 이성관계도 피해왔지
So you'd have an excuse
for not having a relationship.
'아빤 내가 필요해'
'마리는 내가 필요해' 라는 식으로
"Dad needs me. Marie needs me." Now I don't
need you any more, you can't handle it!
하지만, 난 언니가 필요 없어
- 난 자신을 희생했어
- 그럼, 그만해! 엄만 오래 전에 돌아가셨어
- I made sacrifices because...
- Then stop! Mom died a long time ago!
So get your own life and stay outta mine!
We are not cancelling this wedding!
이젠 언니 인생을 살고
내 인생에 참견 마!
결혼식은 취소 안 해!
치료실에도 없고 동관에도 없으니까
여기 어디 있을 거야
She's not in intensive care or
the east wing. She's gotta be up here.
핵폭까지 얼마나 시간이 있어?
How much time do we have to this nuke?
몰라
- I don't know.
- What if Megan doesn't wanna come with us?
메건이 우리랑 안 가겠다고 하면 어떡해?
I don't know.
모르겠어
That's him.
그 사람이야
매트슨 씨
Mr Matheson?
The MRI confirmed that the pressure on
the brain was the result of the concussion.
MRI 결과 두뇌부위의 손상원인은
충격에 의한 것으로 밝혀졌습니다
Meaning?
무슨 뜻이죠?
That we won't release her until questions
about the sources of her injuries are resolved.
충격의 원인을 알아낼 때까지
퇴원시키지 않을 겁니다
Of course. Listen, I just wanna
do what's best for my little girl.
물론이죠
저희 딸 걱정뿐이랍니다
좋아요
Good. I'll check in on her
at the end of my rounds.
회진 후에 다시 오겠습니다
그리고 매트슨 씨
And, Mr Matheson, no cellphones in the
hospital. They interfere with the equipment.
병원에서는 장비들과 충돌이
있으니 핸드폰 쓰지 마세요
Of course. Sorry.
네
(dials phone)
아빠, 아직도 저한테 화나셨어요?
Daddy, are you still mad at me?
아니야, 괜찮아
아빠가 좀 피곤해서 그래
No, sweetie, no. Everything's fine.
Daddy's just tired.
You need to get dressed, OK?
옷 입어야 돼, 알았지?
- 매트슨 씨 사무실입니다
- 첼시, 나야
- Mr Matheson's office.
- Chelsea, it's me.
Do something for me. Book me two seats
on the next flight to Mexico City.
지금 당장 멕시코 행
다음 비행기 두 자리 예약해줘
- But you have a meeting...
- I know. I'm asking you to cancel it.
- 멕시코요? 미팅은...
- 미팅 있는 거 알아
취소해 줄 수 있겠지?
- What about your five o'clock?
- Cancel everything.
- 5시 건요?
- 모두 취소해
(door opens)
Who is the man in Visalia?
바셀리아에 있는 사람이 누구야?
바셀리아에 있는 사람이 누구야!
마무드 파힌
Mamud Faheen.
The man in Visalia is Mamud Faheen.
바셀리아에 있는 사람은 마무드 파힌이에요
뉴스도 아니네, 이미 아는 이름이야
That's not news! We've got his name!
But you don't know where he is. I do.
어디 있는지는 모르잖아요, 난 알아요
- What's the history of the relationship?
- He introduced me to Wald.
관계가 어떻게 시작된 거지?
그가 날 월드한테 소개시켜 줬어요
그래서 월드가 이 건물 도면을 산 거군
So Wald could buy the schematics
for CTU and blow it up as a diversion?
교란용으로 CTU를 폭파하려고?
핵 공격 계획이 있는지는 몰랐어요
I didn't know it was part of a plan
to detonate a nuclear device.
그럼 파힌이 관계된 걸 어떻게 확신하지?
Then why are you so sure
Faheen's involved?
I heard hints that he was involved
in something in Los Angeles.
내가 체포되기 직전에, 파힌이 LA에서
뭔가 큰 일을 꾸민다는 힌트를 들었어요
Something substantial.
지금 바셀리아 어디에 있지?
Where is he in Visalia now?
거기 가기 전까진
위치를 가르쳐 줄 수 없어요
I'm not gonna give you his location
until we get there.
(click)
그걸 알면 내가 필요 없잖아요
If you could get to him, you wouldn't need
me. My deal would do me no good if I'm dead.
죽고 나면 내 사면장도 소용없을 거고
Get me Visalia.
바셀리아로 가야겠네
각하
Sir...
쉐리 말이 맞더군요
Sherry was right. An evacuation of
military personnel began about an hour ago,
군 요원과 물자가 한 시간 전부터
대피를 시작해서 한창 진행 중입니다
which means it is well under way.
- Do we know where this order came from?
- Yes, we do, sir. Roger Stanton.
이 지시가 어디서 내려갔는지 아나?
네, 압니다
로저 스탠튼입니다
Countermand the evacuation.
내 권한으로 대피 명령 취소시키고
대피 중인 군 요원들은 즉시
기지로 복귀하도록 해
All forces already moving are to
return to their bases immediately.
Yes, sir.
네, 각하
Roger. My office, please.
로저
내 사무실로 들어오게!
Janet? Hi, this is Lynne. I'm gonna need
contacts for the following bases:
Point Mugu, Camp Pendleton.
로저, 방금 LA에서 군 물자가
빠져나가고 있다는 소식을 들었네
I got word that military resources
were being moved out of LA.
네, 각하
- Yes.
- On your order.
자네가 지시했고?
Yes. I was implementing the plan.
I assumed you authorised it.
네, 제가 승인했습니다
각하께서 허가하신 줄 알았습니다
No, I told Rayburn not to
trigger any evacuation.
레이번한테 어떤 대피 조치도
하지 말라고 했어
I should have double-checked everything
Rayburn told me before I took any action.
레이번이 했던 말들을
확인했어야 했는데..
Mr President, it's inexcusable.
I take full responsibility.
각하, 용납되지 않습니다
제가 모든 책임을 지겠습니다
We'll worry about that later.
그건 나중에 걱정하고...
린한테 대피 지시를 취소하라고 했네
I just told Lynne to countermand
the evacuation order.
- 즉시 조치되도록 책임지게
- 네, 각하
- Make sure it happens immediately.
- Right away, sir.
- 무엇을 도와드릴까요, 각하?
- 그래
- (secretary) Can I help you, Mr President?
- Yes. Tell Sherry I'll meet her in 20 minutes.
- 쉐리한테 20분 내에 간다고 하게
- 네, 각하
You know how much
Daddy loves you, don't you?
아빠가 널 얼마나 사랑하는지 알지?
And you know how sorry I am that
my little angel ever got hurt, right?
그리고 널 다치게 해서
내 마음이 얼마나 아픈지도 알지?
우린 지금 가야 해
Listen, pal, we're leaving now, OK?
알겠지?
So if anybody tries to talk to you,
you just... you don't say a word. OK?
누가 너한테 말 걸면
넌 그냥, 말은 하지 말고
Just pretend you're asleep.
You can do that, right?
가만히 잠든 척 해
할 수 있지?
네
- OK.
- (door opens)
- Mr Matheson?
매트슨 씨
There's a call for you.
전화 와있어요
전화요?
A call?
간호사실에서 받으세요
- You can take it at the nurse's station.
- Why can't I take it in here?
왜 여기서 못 받죠?
주문 안 하시면
병실에 전화가 없으니까요
Because we don't have phones
in the rooms unless you order one.
거기 가만히 있어, 알았지?
You stay there, OK?
메건, 움직이지마
Megan, don't move.
- Looks like she'll be fine.
- OK.
- 그녀는 괜찮아 보여요
- 네
- OK? Just running a few other tests.
- Is it gonna be much longer?
- 몇 가지 테스트만 하면 됩니다
- 오래 걸리나요?
The phone's right in there.
전화는 바로 안에 있어요
So let's go take a look, OK?
- This is Gary Matheson.
- (Miguel) Mr Matheson?
게리 매트슨입니다
- 어, 매트슨 씨?
- 네, 누구시죠?
- Yeah, who is this?
- This is Trey in Accounts Receivable.
저는 트레이 윌리엄스입니다만
Our computers crashed, and we lost
a lot of your billing information.
저희 컴퓨터가 다운돼서
청구정보가 손실되었습니다
그래서 다시 조사해야 하는데요
So if we could just go over it again...
다음에 하면 안될까요?
- Can we do this another time, please?
- No, we need it now, sir.
안 됩니다, 지금 필요합니다
I can send someone up
to your daughter's room.
원하시면 따님 방으로
사람을 보내겠습니다
No. What do you need?
아니요, 뭐가 알고 싶으시죠?
- Hi, Kim.
- Hi, sweetie.
안녕, 킴
안녕, 아가
자
- Listen, do you trust me?
- Yes.
언니 믿어?
응
I need to get you outta here.
널 데리고 나가야 하는데
이유는 말할 수 없어
내가 말할 수 있는 건, 널 사랑하고
All I can tell you is I'm doing this because
I love you and I want you to be safe. OK?
너의 안전을 위해서라는 거야
알았어
OK.
가자
Come on.
- The expiration date?
- It expires March 2007, OK?
만기일은요?
- 2007년 3월입니다, 됐어요?
- 좋아요
Great. Now if we could just
go over your billing address.
그럼 청구지 주소 확인 좀...
아니
You know what? I'll come down later.
다음에 들를게요
Mr Matheson?
매트슨 씨?
메건
Megan?
- My daughter's gone.
- Did you try the bathroom?
- 내 딸이 방에 없어요
- 화장실은 보셨어요?
- 네, 없어졌어요
- 방사선과에 갔을 수도 있어요
- Yes. She's not there.
- She might have been taken to radiology.
어디 있는지 알아내요
Well, find out where she is.
Yes, of course.
네, 물론이죠
(woman over PA)
Dr Shapiro, 2262. Dr Shapiro, 2262.
- Where are we going, Kim?
- I told you, you have to trust me.
어디 가는 거야, 킴?
설명할 시간 없어
언니를 믿어
I just got off the phone. Come on.
- 방금 전화 끊었어
- 괜찮아
I changed my mind. I don't wanna go.
아니, 나 안 갈래
My daddy's gonna get really mad, and then
he's gonna hurt me. I don't wanna go.
아빠가 화나서 날 때릴 거야
아빠가 널 때리기 때문에
여기서 나가야 해
We need to go because
your dad is hurting you.
네 엄마도 아빠를 어떻게 할 수가 없어
And your mom is trying to
stop him, but she can't.
He's gonna keep hurting you
unless you leave with us.
우리랑 같이 가지 않으면
계속 널 때릴 거야
이게 아빠를 말리는 유일한 방법이야
That's the only way anyone is gonna
stop him. Do you understand me?
이게 유일한 방법이야
Your daughter's not with
any of the departments.
모든 부서에 연락했는데, 어디에도 없어요
그럼, 대체 어디 있단 말이오?
- Then where is she?
- I'm trying to figure that out.
알아내려고 하잖아요
- 누가 따님 근처에...
- 아니요!
- Did you see anyone near her room?
- No! Call security! Find me my daughter!
경비 불러서 정문 감시하고
내 딸 찾아내요!
Megan, I need you to
breathe and calm down
메건, 숨 크게 쉬고 진정해
눈물 그치고 이제 가자, 응?
and stop crying, so we can leave now. OK?
Come on.
어서
I miss my mom. I want my mom!
엄마 어디 있어? 엄마
그래, 어서
I know. Come on with me. I know.
(radio) Look out for a nine-year-old girl
with blonde hair, striped top and blue jeans.
금발 머리, 아홉 살 소녀, 청바지..
서쪽 문을 둘러보겠습니다
I've got Third Street, west door covered.
In there.
저기 안으로 가자
Just got a team on the ground in Visalia,
and more coming in from Fresno.
바셀리아에 팀을 대기시켰네
프레즈노에서도 지원 갈 거야
지부에서 사람을 보내왔어
밀러랑 같이 가
Division's loaned us some men,
so I'm sending Miller along with you.
혼자 할 수 있어
I can handle her myself.
That's not what I'm worried about.
내가 걱정하는 이유는 다른 데 있어
조지, 내가 나 하나 좋자고
수백만 시민의 목숨을 날리겠어?
Do you think I'd sentence millions to death
just for the satisfaction of killing her?
내 할 일을 할 뿐이야
I'll do my job.
I'm just sending Miller along
to make sure of that.
나도 그걸 확인하려고
밀러를 보내는 거야
(Mason coughing)
You should go be with your family.
가족이랑 같이 있도록 해
비행기 타러 가
You should get on a plane.
- 도착하면 연락할게
- 그래, 좋아
- I'll call you when we're in the air.
- Yeah. Good.
David...
- 데이빗
- 군 대피에 대해선 어떻게 알았지?
How did you find out about
the military evacuation?
I made some phone calls.
소문을 듣고, 전화 몇 통 했어요
Just following up on a rumour.
I can't tell you any more than that.
- 그 이상은 말해줄 수 없어요
- 말 해
You will tell me more,
and I will not ask you again.
두 번 묻지 않겠어
난 당신 부하가 아니에요, 데이빗
I am not a member of your staff, David.
I am your wife.
- 당신 아내라고요
- 전 부인이지
Ex-wife, and you will tell me because
the safety and security of this country
당신의 권력다툼보다
이 나라 시민들의 안전이 우선이야
is more important than your power plays.
이때까지 일어난 일에도 불구하고
You know, despite everything
that's happened, I love you.
- 난 당신을 사랑해요
- 제발
- Oh, please.
- No, I always will.
난 앞으로도 계속 그럴 거예요
당신은 안 믿겠지만,
Whether you believe it or not, everything that
I have done has been in your best interest.
이제까지 내가 해온 일들은
모두 당신을 위해서였어요
If you won't give me
a second chance at your heart,
나한테 다시 기회를 주고 싶지 않다면
내가 도움이라도 줄 수 있게 해줘요
let me help in the ways you know I can.
And I can't help you, David, unless you
give me some idea of what you're facing.
하지만, 무슨 일인지
말해주지 않으면 도울 수 없어요
I was able to find something
your own staff couldn't find.
난 당신 참모들이 몰랐던
정보를 알아낼 수 있었어요
당신에게 알릴 필요도 없었지만
내가 오고 싶어서 온 거예요
I didn't have to warn you.
I came here on my own accord.
Terrorists have planned
a strike against Los Angeles.
테러리스트들이 LA를 공격하려 하고 있어
NSA thinks it'll be today.
NSA는 그게 오늘이 될 거래
What kind of strike?
어떤 공격이요?
핵폭탄
Nuclear.
Oh, my G...
맙소사
Oh, my God.
Talk to me, Sherry.
말해 봐, 쉐리
빨리
Come on.
I got the information about
the military evacuation
군 대피에 관한 정보는
국방부 사람한테 얻었어요
from someone inside
the defence department.
누구?
Who?
고위 관리요, 나한테 빚진 게 있거든요
A high-level staffer. He's in the loop.
He owed me a favour.
But there's something more important.
하지만, 더 중요한 게 있어요
He also told me that there are members of
your own administration allying against you.
정부 내에 당신의
반대하는 세력이 있어요
They want control of your presidency.
당신의 대통령권을 장악하길 원해요
That's why I came here today.
그래서 내가 온 거예요
Who, Sherry?
누구야, 쉐리?
당신 정책에 반대하고, 맘대로
이 나라를 주무르려는 사람들이요
People who disagree with your policies,
who want to impose their will on the country.
There have been deals made under
the table, David. Back-room promises.
당신 몰래 거래가 오갔었어요
Now, I can keep digging, find out.
내가 더 많은 정보를 알아낼 수 있어요
물론, 당신이 내 도움을 원해야겠지만
If you want my help.
If I accept your help, it won't be about us.
당신 도움을 받더라도
우리 관계는 변함없어
나라를 위한 최선책이라 선택하는 거야
It'll be about doing
what's best for the country.
뭐라고 하든 좋아요
Sweetheart, you can call it
anything you want.
I'll get you a secure line
and a private place to make your calls.
보안전화와 전화할 개인공간을 주지
Then I'll come to you
as soon as I find out more.
더 알아내면, 곧바로 갈 게요
당신 장난이 아니길 바라
This had better not be
one of your manipulations.
위험부담이 너무 커
The stakes are too high.
- 아빠
- 응?
- Dad?
- Hm?
레이자 부모님이 오셨어요
- Reza's parents are here.
- I'm on the phone to your grandmother.
할머니랑 통화 중이란다
금방 갈게
- I'll be right there.
- (door bell)
Oh!
오셨군요
You're here!
반가워요
Welcome.
만나서 반가워요, 케이트
- So nice to see you, Kate.
- Come on in.
- 들어가죠
- 고마워요
Thank you. The house looks beautiful.
집이 근사하군요
Oh, thank you.
고마워요
Well... you must be tired.
Let's go into the living room.
피곤하시겠어요
- 거실로 가도록 하죠
- 네
OK.
다들 괜찮아요?
So, how is everyone holding up?
Not too bad.
나쁘진 않죠
Where is Reza?
레이자는 어디 있죠?
Um, well, there's a small problem
we're dealing with.
약간의 문제가 있어요
What kind of problem?
무슨 문제요?
Um, some men from the government
are here talking to him.
정부에서 사람이 나와서 얘기 중이에요
뭐에 대해서?
About?
- It's a criminal investigation.
- I don't understand.
- 범죄 수사예요
- 범죄 수사? 이해가 안 돼요
- It's very complicated.
- Kate, what is going on?
- 아주 복잡해요
- 케이트, 대체 무슨 일이에요?
- It would be best if Reza told you himself.
- Told us what?
레이자한테 직접 들으시는 게 좋겠어요
뭘 들으라는 거요?
They're talking to Reza about his possible
involvement in terrorist activities.
레이자의 테러 운동 가담 여부에
대해서 얘기 중이에요
- 말도 안 돼요
- 무슨 오해일 거예요
- That is absurd!
- This must be a mistake.
- That's what they're trying to find out.
- You see?
그걸 알아내려는 중이죠
Your country, you talk about tolerance,
you talk about freedom,
당신 나라는 자유니 관용이니 하지만
but you treat every Middle Easterner
like terrorist!
모든 중동사람들을 테러리스트 취급해요
아녜요, 그럴 리가요
No! No, of course not.
I'm sure it'll all get sorted out.
별일 아니라서 금방 끝날 것 같아요
- Rima, Hassan...
- Bob, do you know about this?
밥, 무슨 일인지 알아요?
They just showed up about an hour ago.
I know nothing else. I'm sorry.
한 시간 전에 왔다는 것밖엔
저도 아는 게 없어요, 미안해요
걱정 마세요, 별일 없을 거예요
Don't worry. I'm sure it's nothing.
주차장에서 기다려
Wait for me in the parking lot.
10분 이상 지체되면, 잡힌 걸로 알고
If it's more than ten minutes, it means
they caught me, so take off without me.
나 없이 그냥 가
그럴 수 없어, 우린 다 같이 갈 거야
You can't let them.
We are gonna leave all together.
알았지?
OK?
Miguel.
미겔
Thank you.
고마워
혼자 걸을 수 있겠어?
Are you OK to walk by yourself?
그래? 좋아
Yeah? Good girl.
Hey! Hey!
20대 남자 하나가 모니터를 들고 달아났다
I got a male Hispanic, early 20s,
running out with a computer monitor.
Hey, come on!
Shh.
Go that way!
저 쪽으로 가!
So, Ed, how are ya?
에디, 잘 지내?
Don't bother, Nina.
상관 마, 니나
I'm here because I have to be,
not because I'm your friend.
네 친구라서 여기 있는 게 아니야
You're here because they think, after I help
stop the bomb, Jack will try to kill me.
맞아, 폭탄을 찾은 후에
잭이 날 죽일까봐 여기 있는 거겠지
Which, of course, he will.
당신이 잭을 막지 못하면 어떡하지?
And what if you can't stop him?
I mean, no offence,
에디, 기분 나쁘게 듣지 마
but, Ed, let's face it, you're no match for Jack.
솔직히 잭한테 안 되잖아
You're just not that ruthless.
당신은 그렇게 냉정하지 못해
잭이 당신 모르게
방아쇠를 당기면 어떻게 될까?
So he manages to get around you
and pull the trigger. What happens then?
Because of the pardon, he knows if he
kills me, he'll spend the rest of his life in jail.
날 죽이면 남은 인생을
감옥에서 보내야 될 거야
Jack, if you have some way to
shut her up I'm not thinking of...
잭, 어떻게 니나 입 좀 닥치게 해봐
Of course, Jack's mind is thinking
"That's not such a bad deal."
물론, 잭은 아무것도 아니라고 생각하겠지
Small price to pay to avenge his wife's death.
아내의 복수에 대한 대가로
나쁘지 않다고
But what about his daughter?
Is he thinking about her?
하지만, 그의 딸은 어떨까?
딸 생각을 할까?
She's already lost one parent.
If he kills me, she'll have no one.
이미 부모 한 명을 잃었고
잭이 날 죽이면, 가족이라곤 아무도 없을 텐데
Jack knows I'm right.
잭은 내 말이 옳다는 걸 알아
폭탄을 찾는데 날 이용하고 나면
He should just use me to stop the bomb,
and then go home to Kim.
킴이 있는 집으로 돌아가야 해
She needs you, Jack.
킴은 당신이 필요해요, 잭
- I didn't transfer that money.
- You transferred it into that account.
- 난 아무것도...
- 그 계좌로 송금했잖소
- 난 송금하지..
- 난 송금한 적 없어요!
- 그럼, 누가 했는지 말해요
I didn't!
Then you better tell me who did,
or I'm taking you in!
그렇지 않으면, 체포할 거요
왜 이러는 겁니까?
Why are you doing this?
Friends of mine...
오늘 내 동료들이...
시민들을 지키려고 최선을
다하다가 폭파로 죽고 말았소
who were doing their best to protect
the citizens of this country
were murdered today... probably by
the same people you're funding!
당신이 지원하는 사람들 때문에!
That a good enough reason for you?
이 정도면 충분합니까?
얘기했듯이
I told you before...
더 이상은 몰라요
I don't know anything else.
당신 부모님이군요
Your parents.
All right, stand up, Reza.
일어나요
머리 뒤로 손 올리세요
Place your hands behind your head.
It's a shame. It's gonna break their heart.
안됐군요, 실망시켜드릴 테니
I have to walk you right past them.
바로 옆으로 지나갈 겁니다
And they're gonna see who their son really is.
아들이 진짜 어떤 사람인지
보게 될 겁니다
Wait!
잠깐만요
I confirmed the transfers,
but I didn't make them.
송금은 인정해요
하지만, 내가 한 건 아니에요
I was just covering the records.
전 기록을 숨겼을 뿐이에요
I didn't want him to get into trouble.
그가 곤란해지는 걸 원치 않았어요
누구요? 누구를 보호하는 겁니까?
Who? Who are you covering for?
누가 사이에드 알리 계좌로 송금한 겁니까?
Come on, who transferred that money
into Syed Ali's accounts?
밥 워너
Bob Warner.
마리의 아버지요
Marie's father.
- (Megan groans)
- What?
왜?
- What's the matter?
- I don't feel very well.
- 뭐야?
- 몸이 안 좋아
이리와
Come on, Miguel.
미겔, 빨리...
- (screams)
- Get away from us!
- 저리 가요
- 나한테 보내, 킴
Give her to me, or I will make sure
you go to prison for 20 years.
20년 동안 감옥에 처박아 놓고 말 거야
상관없어요, 메건이
어떻게 다쳤는지 아니까요
- I know how she got hurt.
- That was an accident!
- 사고였어
- 칼라의 상처들처럼 말이에요?
Like Carla's bruises?
(Megan screams)
- It's OK.
- Miguel...
(Miguel) Let's just get outta here.
어서 가자
게리의 차 열쇠 찾아봐
Get his car keys.
(speaking Arabic)
- Reza.
- Sweetheart, angel.
- 레이자?
- 오! 마리
- You OK?
- Yes.
- 괜찮아?
- 응
- They know I didn't do anything.
- Oh, thank God.
- 저들도 내 잘못이 아닌 줄 알아
- 다행이야
- We can get married today.
- I don't know, sweetheart.
결혼식 할 수 있겠다
Mr Warner.
워너 씨
Could you follow me, please, sir?
이쪽으로 들어오시겠어요?
- What does this have to do with me?
- Just come with me, please.
- 저랑 무슨 상관입니까?
- 일단 들어오시죠
뭐라고 말한 거야?
What did you tell them?
진실
The truth.
- The truth? What do you mean, the truth?
- Please, my parents are very upset.
- 진실? 무슨 말이야?
- 제발! 우리 부모님이 많이 화나 계셔
(Kim) Hurry.
Yeah.
Yeah. OK.
The team's in Visalia.
We'll have tactical and field units.
바셀리아에 작전
현장 요원들이 배치된대
준비됐는지 확인했어?
We have confirmation that they're in place?
아마 비행 중일 거야
Probably in the air.
항공 운항...
We'll have air traffic, um...
Air traffic priority?
항공 운항 우선권?
응
Yeah...
Tra...
Jack...
It's all right, Ed. It's all right. Just take it easy.
괜찮아
한글번역
황우성(myjason@nate.com)
자막편집/싱크
남효주(hyojunet@nate.com)
번역수정
강은규(kangek@nate.com)
최종수정
이수경(soo5684@nate.com)
동호회 외 무단유출을 금지합니다
(http://club.nate.com/24)
Visiontext Subtitles: Tram Nguyen Zelniker
English SDH